# Elena Stefanovski

Economic Department of finance and credit Menagement

Goce Delcev 69 s.Kravari Bitola, N.Macedonia (±389) 72247320 ⊠ stefanovskielena@gmail.com

#### Personal

I consider my self a highly motivated, decisive and reliable person. I always strive to improve and supplement my knowledge, but also to implement it trought assigned tasks and goals during the work process. My motto at work is implementing solutions, instead of pointing out problems. Over the years and the acquired experience, i have learned to work under pressure and in a dynamic environment, which is one of my great advantages and with which i belive that i will be able to contribute a lot to your company, together with my ambition, determination and skills for organization and planning.

### Work Experience

2011 - 2015 Sales Assistent, DPTU DE-TA Dejan - Skopje.

Task: Customer service in the sales hall, reception and display of goods according to the company's standards, organization and arrangment of warehouse space, other work tasks related to daily functioning

2015 - 2022 Organizational unit Menager, DPTU DE-TA Dejan - Skopje.

Task: Customer service in the sales hall, reception and display of goods according to the company's standards,organization and arrangement of warehouse space,other work tasks related to daily functioning

#### Skills and Expertise

, Highly organized, self motivated individual who can work independently as well as work effectively in a collaborative team environment Leadership skills,as well as coaching and team building Motivate/inspire empoyees to support the company vision Excellent professional/Executive skills Recognazied leader in business development and client relationship development Complete understating of production, quality and cost Skills advanced capabilities in web researching Critical thinking.

#### **Training**

Courses and Work ethic, Introducing to communication, Active listening, Body Language, Social Seminars style, Consultative sales and mentoring

#### Education

2006-2011 Graduated to the Faculty of Econonics Menagment, finance - credit, International Slavic University "Gavrilo Romanovich Derzhavin" - Bitola, .

## Languages

English excellent Serbian exellent

Macedonian native speaker